<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MIYOSHA — Mindful Youth Shaping</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MIYOSHA — Mindful Youth Shaping</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-us/</guid>
      <description>Vision and Mission We envision our youth as motivated, skilled, and responsible young people who are ready to build their country, Tanzania.
We seek to enhance their social, cultural, and economic situations through engagement in sports, recreational and artistic activities, life skills education, and income generating activities.
Objectives  Register and group youth and confer them ownership of their organization. Offer sports and artistic activities, playing facilities, and equipment for youth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Information Pursuant to § 5 TMG for Germany:
Mindful Youth Shaping (MIYOSHA)
Matembele II Street, Kivule Ward, Ilala
P.O. Box 22013
+255 762 140 881
info[at]miyosha[dot]org
Registered under the Non-Governmental Organization Act, 2002,
with Registration No. 00NGO/00009902
Represented by Paul Gogo, Chairman</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Income Generation</title>
      <link>/income-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/income-generation/</guid>
      <description>Vocational Training With the generous support of the German Internationaler Club der Schlitzohren e.V., MIYOSHA has been offering sewing machine training courses to youth in Kivule Ward, Ilala Municipal Council, in Dar es Salaam since July 2015.
By December 2019, 173 youth had already benefitted from our courses, which typically run six days per week for six months.
Course graduates receive continued support from MIYOSHA and the local community, helping them make the most of their newly acquired skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Skills</title>
      <link>/life-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/life-skills/</guid>
      <description>Health Counseling Our health education efforts include the following activities:
  Group Counseling Sessions
Here, we educate our youth on health issues and discourage them from engaging in risky behaviour, i.e., alcohol and drug abuse or unsafe sex.
  Individual Counseling Sessions
Here, we offer our youth one-on-one support with their personal problems.
  Recreational Activities
Our sports and arts offerings form an integral part of our health education as they both encourage and are encouraged by a healthy lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports and Arts</title>
      <link>/sports-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sports-arts/</guid>
      <description>Regular Sports Offerings In our sports teams, MIYOSHA youth train their collaborative and competitive spirits.
We currently offer soccer (football), basketball, and netball.
Our teams are grouped into three different age categories: Kids, Juniors, and Seniors.
They regularly play other teams in the region, and our soccer teams have been very successful both at the regional and at the national level.
In addition to the regular matches, we organize several MIYOSHA sports weekends per year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>